Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters
  - Dramatic Council Production--The Young Idea, Un-dated; 506-30; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Theater Fund Follies, Un-dated; 506-36; 11x14 (Box A2)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Two's Company, Un-dated; 506-28; 14x20 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Production--Yellow Jack, Un-dated; 506-15; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Dramatic Council Production- Wings Over Europe, Un-datedd; 506-14; 14x18 inches (Box B1)
  - Dramatic Council Productions--"Alison's House" by Susan Glaspell, Un-dated; 506-35; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
    Dramatic Council Productions
  - Dramatic Council Productions- "Mrs. Bumpstead- Leigh", Un-dated; 506-24; 14 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Dramatic Council Productions- "The Green Goddess", 1926; 506-2; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Dramatic Reading: "The Barretts of Wimpole Street." by Mrs. Guy Stevens Farrington., Un-dated; 393; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Driven Back to Egypt, Un-dated; 905-21; 14 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Dying For Him", 1938; 5035; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - E PLURIBUS UNUM? American National Identity/Identities, 1996; 905-86; 17x22 inches (Box C3)
  - E Pluribus Unum? American National Indentity/Identities. February 8-10, 1996. Keynote adresses by Arthur Schlesinger, Jr. and Lani Guinier., 905-86; 22 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - "East Lynne" or "How Far Can a Good Girl Go?", 1946; 5082; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - East-West Trade Conference, 1966; 2081; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Eastern Orthodox Campus Organization, 1968; 5181; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Ed Reinecke--Bob Keyes, 1969; 365; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Education for Democratic Action. A Series of discussions with members of the Highlander Research and Education Center and Herb Kohl. Organized by the School of Education [and others] ca. 1981, 2006-046; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Eight Annual Tour: Stanford University Glee and Mandolin Clubs, 1904; 524-14; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - El Cento Chicano-You Don't Look Mexican: a play by Julie Padilla presented by El Centro Chicano, 36120; 532-1; 11x17 (Box map case)
    Drama
  - El Centro Chicano. Colores de una Cultura. Cinco de Mayo at Stanford, n.d possibly 1985; 532-3; 11x17 (Box map case)
    design by Burciaga
  - El Centro Chicano. Posada en Stanford. Posada procession-mariachis-pinatas-Ballet Foklorico., 32843; 532-2; 11x17 (Box map case)
  - El Centro Chicano. Viva el Cinco de Mayo! Estanford, 1989; 532-6; 11x17 (Box map case)
  - El Centro Chicano. Cinco de Mayo, 1993 Stanford University (calendar of events), 52307; 22 x 16 inches (Box not specified)
  - El Centro Chicano. Fiesta de los Muertos. Celebration of the Dead, 1985; 532-5; 11x17 (Box map case)
  - El Centro Chicano. La Gran Posada, 36134; 532-4; 8.5x14 (Box map case)
  - El Centro Chicano. Movimiento Estudiatil Chicano de Aztlan 5 de mayo, 1991. A Stanford Cenennial Multicultural Event., 532-08; 18 x 24 inches (Box not specified)
  - El Mes de la Chicana [list of events from Feb. 4--March 11 [probably 1982], 2006-053; 17 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Election notice for SCLC positions, recommending Rick Atkins, Yale Baunstein, and Jeff Kane, May 27, 1969, 905-62; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Election Results, Un-dated; 905-17; 13 x 18 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Elektra", 1938; 5031; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Elementary Particles? A University Lecture by Murray Gell-Mann, 1968; 353; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Elements of Life: Faces of Races in Multiple Spaces. A roving site specific exploration, initiated by collaborators of Dance of Race and Enviornment. Wed / June 2 / 7pm The Shumway Fountain at Green Library entrance, 2010-; 2010-010; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - Eliot Richardson, 1965; 330; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Elizabethan Carnival and Ruff House", 1902-; 513-4; 20 x 28 inches (Box C7)
  - Elway Cardinal Jersey #7 Retirement, 2013 Nov 7; 2015-008; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
    Elway, John
  - Emerging Africa! Stanford African Students' Association presents Africa Week at Stanford. [schedule of events 16th-23rd of April], 2006-; 2010-004; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - Emerging Subjectivities in Chicana Literature: Madres, Comadres, Madrinas y Quinceaneras. A Literary Series by Chicana authors. Apr. 15--May 20, 1997, 212-4; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Empowerment, 5 de Mayo, 1984 (calendar of events for Cinco de Mayo at Stanford), 530-30; 10.75 x 20.5 inches (Box C9)
  - Empowerment, 5 de Mayo, 1984 (Calendar of events for Cinco de Mayo at Stanford), 530-30; 10.75 x 20.5 inches (Box not specified)
  - Encina Hall--rules and regulations, circa 1900; 1; 16 x 7 inches (Box A1)
  - Encina and Toyon Information and Regulations [possibly printed 1947], 39817; 3.75 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - End CBW resarch. End Counter-Insurgency research. End research related to the war in Southeast Asia. Establish closer relations with SRI. Dig It? Show it Boycott, 1969 May 12; 527-06; 11 x 17 inches (Box C4)
  - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution--30th Anniversary of the Mouse (photo of Engelbart and first mouse) 1998 Dec. 9, 20118; 24 x 36 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
    Copy 6 is signed
  - Engelbart's Unfinished Revolution (timeline) 1998 Dec. 9, 20117; 11 x 25 inches (Box D1)
  - Ernest F. Fenollosa Lecture: "The Five Period of Japanese Art.", Un-dated; 382; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Ernest Seton-Thompson Lecture: Personality of Wild Animals", 1901-; 308; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Ernesto Galarza Commemorative Lecture by Thomas Saenz and Chicano/Latino Community Awards. Friday, May 14, 2010-., 2010-002; 12 x 18 inches (Box B3)
  - Ernesto Galarza's Legacy on the History of Labor Migration. Ninth Annual Ernesto Galarza Commemmorative Lecture. Jorge A. Bustamante, 1994; 9083; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Ernesto Galarza's Legacy on the History of Labor Migration. Ninth Annual Ernesto Galarza Commemorative Lecture. Jorge A. Bustamante., 1994; 90803; 11 x 17 inches (Box not specified)
  - Ethnicity, Equity,& Environment: Confronting a Global Dilemma, 1991 Apr 11-14; 2015-029; 16 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - "Every Man in his Humour", 1905-; 5071; 10 x 12 inches (Box A3)
  - "Every Man in his Humour", 1905-; 5072; 10 x 12 inches (Box 341 map case)
    two copies- 507-1
  - "Everyman", 1903-; 513-11; 19 x 13 inches (Box C7)
  - Exceptional Student, The, 1941; 8; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Faculty Club Presents The Spy, Un-dated; 123; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
    Faculty/Staff -- Drama
  - Faculty Dramatic Club, Un-dated; 126; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Faculty Dramatic Club: "All in a Fog, or Who is Who?", 1898; 103; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Faculty Farce: The Red Vampire, 1900; 105; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Fall Quarter '76 SWOPSI Film Series. Labor History: the struggle to organize, 1976; 2006-010; 10.25 x 16.75 inches (Box B2)
  - "Fashion", Un-dated; 511-47; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "Fashion", Un-dated; 513-68; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Father Brown, Detective", Un-dated; 530-16; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Father Dan Berrigan, 1968; 351; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Feminicide = Sanctioned Murder. Gender, Race & Violence in Global Context. Stanford University May 16-19, 2007, 39451; 15 x 23 inches (Box GW403)
    see also SC0898
  - Festival of Contemporary Music, 1967; 202-29; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Fiesta Delos Muertos Celebration of the Dead, Un-dated; 532-05; 11x17 (Box A2)
  - Fifteenth Annual Carnot Debate, 1909; 521-1; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - "Finian's Rainbow", Un-dated; 513-44; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Fire Whistles, circa 1905-1910; 3; 13 x 6 inches (Box A1)
  - First Lecture on Mexico, 1899; 104; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - First Year at Stanford, Un-dated; 905-20; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - FOB David Henry Hwang's Obie award-winning play. Feb. 17-20, 2010-. Asian Amnerican Theater Project. Stanford Asian Pacific American Alumni Club. Signed by David Henry Hwang, 2010-017; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
    program from event in 4digit collection; 7841
  - Football--2011 Home Schedule, 2010-2011; 2011-005; 14 x 22 inches (Box B2)
  - Football--3 Games this Week, Un-dated; 801-52; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
    Football.
  - Football--Annual Intercollegiate Freshman Game, 1903-; 801-17; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Buy a Season Ticket, 1900; 801-11; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--California vs. Stanford, Un-dated; 801-26; 11x19 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--California vs. Stanford, 1900; 801-10; 13x20 inches (Box map case)
  - Football--California vs. Stanford Freshmen, 1905-; 801-21; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Football--Chemawa Indians vs Stanford, Un-dated; 801-63; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--First Game Stanford vs Olympics, Un-dated; 801-39; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Football Friday and Saturday, 1989; 801-3; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Football Tickets--Stanford vs. California, 1898; 801-4; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Football--Fort Baker vs. Stanford, 1903-; 801-18; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Foster Farms Bowl: Go Stanford, undated; 2015-018 (Box A6)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Belmont, Un-dated; 801-50; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Oakland High, Un-dated; 801-64; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Palo alto High, Un-dated; 801-55; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Palo Alto High School, Un-dated; 801-42; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Santa Clara, Un-dated; 801-32; 14x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Santa Clara College, Un-dated; 801-71; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Santa Clara College, Un-dated; 801-73; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Freshmen vs St. Mary's, Un-dated; 801-41; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Freshmen vs Tamalpais Military Academy, Un-dated; 801-65; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs. Barbarians, 1898; 801-2; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs. Berkeley High School, 1901-; 801-15; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs. Hoitts School, Un-dated; 801-33; 14x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs. Palo Alto, 1904; 801-20; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen vs. Palo Alto High, Un-dated; 801-53; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Freshmen vs. San Mateo, 1899; 801-8; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Freshmen Will Play Santa Clara College, 1901-; 801-14; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--League of the Cross Cadets vs. Stanford University, Un-dated; 801-25; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Mr. Tamalpais vs. Freshmen, 1899; 801-6; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Multnomah Club vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-48; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Multnomah vs Stanford, Un-dated; 801-74; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Football--Multnomah vs. Stanford, Un-dated; 801-34; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Nevada vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-75; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Oakland High School, Un-dated; 801-61; 9 1/2x2 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Olympic vs Varisty, Un-dated; 801-66; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Oregon State Univ. vs. Varsity, Un-dated; 801-46; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Pensacola vs Stanford, Un-dated; 801-36; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Football--Pensacola vs Stanford, Un-dated; 801-51; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Pensacola vs Stanford, Un-dated; 801-67; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Pensacola vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-49; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Reliance Athletic Club vs Stanford Varsity, Un-dated; 801-62; 91/2x12 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Reliance vs Stanford, Un-dated; 801-60; 9 1/2x12 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Reliance vs. Stanford, Un-dated; 801-30; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Sherman Indians vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-44; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Southern California vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-69; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford Football '86 Schedule, Un-dated; 801-80; inches (Box map case)
    5/98 in 341 map case
  - Football--Stanford Plays Oregon Saturday, Un-dated; 801-47; 22x28 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford Varsity vs. Kansas Volunteers, Un-dated; 801-24; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Stanford vs Army (of San Francisco), Un-dated; 801-59; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Stanford vs California, Un-dated; 801-27; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs California Nov. 22 (1997) 100th Big Game, 801-79; 18x24 inches (Box C3)
  - Football--Stanford vs Nevada, Un-dated; 801-72; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. California, Un-dated; 801-5; 7x28 inches (Box A4)
  - Football--Stanford vs. California, 1899; 801-9; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - Football--Stanford vs. California, 1905-; 801-22; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. California, Un-dated; 801-29; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Naval Cadets, 1903-; 801-16; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Nevada, 1899; 801-7; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Nevada, Un-dated; 801-31; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Olympics, Un-dated; 801-1; 12x21 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Olympics, 1901-; 801-13; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Football--Stanford vs. Olympics, Un-dated; 801-28; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Thanksgiving Number, 1903-; 801-19; 20x26 inches (Box map case)
  - Football--The BIG Game, 1892-1992, 801-77; 12x19 inches (Box C9)
    #807/6000--Signed by artist
  - Football--The KSFO Cardinal Sooner Fair. Stanford University Angell Field, 1983; 801-78; 17.75x23 inches (Box D2)
  - Football--"This is how WE do it!" Schedule, 2012; 2015-019; 12 x 18 inches (Box B4)
  - Football--Univ. of Oregon vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-45; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--University of Nevada vs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-70; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Utah A.C. cs Varsity, Un-dated; 801-57; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity Intercollegiate Football; Stanford vs. California, 1905 Nov 11; 2015-031; 14 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - Football--Varsity vs 15th Infantry of Monterey Presidio, 1905-; 801-76; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity vs Barbarians, Un-dated; 801-37; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity vs Barbarians, Un-dated; 801-40; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity vs Barbarians, Freshmen vs. St. Mary's, Un-dated; 801-54; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity vs Olympics, Freshmen vs. Berkeley High, Freshmen vs. Mission High, Un-dated; 801-56; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity vs Reliance, Un-dated; 801-68; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--Varsity vs. Olympics, Un-dated; 801-43; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football--What's Bruin?, 1969; 801-23; 11x16 inches (Box A4)
  - Football -Stanford vs Reliance, Un-dated; 801-58; 14x11 inches (Box A4)
  - Football -Stanford vs. Reliance, 1900; 801-12; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football -Stanford vs. Reliance, Un-dated; 801-35; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football -Stanford vs. Reliance, Un-dated; 801-38; 14x22 inches (Box C9)
  - Football Show: "The College Widower", 1907; 513-14; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Football Stanvord vs. Olympics. Saturday November 4th, 1901-; 801-13; 14 x 22 inches (Box B1)
  - Football-Football Tickets-Stanford v. California, November 24,1898 2:30 p.m.; 801-4; 11x14 (Box map case)
  - Fortunato Duranti, 1965; 11; 22x16 inches (Box C1)
  - Founders and Educators: Creating a Modern University. Stanford University Archives, May 10 to August 31, 1986., 20116; 22 x 12 inches (Box C1)
  - The Four Faces of Blackness II, Oct 17-19 (Box C6)
  - Four One-Act Plays, Un-dated; 502-2; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Four One-Act Plays, Un-dated; 502-5; 7 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Frank Lloyd Wright's Hanna House: The Visiion Renewed. A Symposium in celebration of the Reopening. Wednesday April 14, 1999, 2003-031; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Free University of Berlin, Un-dated; 530-17; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Free you be-in / El Camino Park, Palo Alto / All day Sunday, September 29 [1968], 905-54; 11x17 inches (Box B2)
  - Freedom and Responsibility, Un-dated; 409; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Frehsman Intercollegiate Rugby Football: Stanford vs. California, Un-dated; 805-18; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
    Athletics -- Rugby
  - From the gallery six to Stanford celebrating 50 years of beat literature with Michael McClure (Thursday June 1, 2006-). With funding from Student Initiated Courses and the Creative Writing Department., 2006-057; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Frosh-Soph Jamboree, 1955; 519-1; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Fuji Comes to Stanford. Word Graphics... invites you to an open house.. .April 13, 1984, 2002-004 (Box C3)
    Features front view of Quad with Mt. Fuji behind it.
  - G.I.'s and Veterans March for Peace, San Francisco October 12 1968. One piece printed by the march organization with 2 handouts from Stanford groups., 905-51; 8.5 x 14 and 8.5 x 11 (Box A3)
  - G.I.'s March for Peace, 1968; 905-52; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - G.I.'s March for Peace, 1968; 905-52; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - Gaieties 2002. The Quadfather. Stanford. It's more than a school...It's a family. Ram's Head Theatrical Society, 2003-015; 18 x 24 inches (Box C4)
    Has tape on it and one untaped tear.
  - Gaieties 99. Farm Wars: The Berkeley Menace. Ram's Head Theatrical Society., 1999; 2003-038; 18 x 24 inches (Box D1)
  - Gaieties of '45 "A Girl in Every Port" [includes cast list, crew list, credits for each muscial piece], 1945; 2006-063; 13 x 20 inches (Box C4)
  - Gaities: "Stanford's Gone G.I.", 509-13; 28 x 20 inches (Box D2)
  - Gala Revival of the 1845 comedy with songs: "Fashion of Life in New York", Un-dated; 513-20; 14 x 21.5 inches (Box C7)
  - Gender, race and class in society. The Jing Lyman Lectures, Spring 1982, 2162; 17 x 22 inches (Box D2)
    Inst. for Research on Women and Gender
  - German Studies--Refiguring Culture: Cinema& Society in Contemporary Berlin, Un-dated; 21301; 11x17 inches (Box A1)
    German Studies
  - Germany: East and West, 1968; 338; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Ghosts"', 1941; 5032; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Gift Horse International Gift Fair, Un-dated; 905-39; 8 1/2 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Gilbert & Sullivan's Trial by Jury plus Puccini's one-act opera Gianni Schicchi, Un-dated; 903-15; 14.5 x 19 inches (Box C10)
    Stanford Savoyards
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs: Fifth Annual Tour, 1900; 524-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs: Fifth Annual Tour, 1899; 524-6; 12 x 18 inches (Box C7)
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs: Sixth Annual Tour, 1901-; 524-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs: Third Annual Tour, 1898; 524-5; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Glee and Mandolin Clubs: First Concert, Un-dated; 524-41; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Globalizing Black History: intellectuals, politics and new approaches to transnationalism. 21 May 2010- Stanford University. [includes day's schedule and speakers], 2010-013; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - GO CARDINAL! The Chronicle. [probably a sign passed out at a game], circa 2000; 2003-027; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - "Goat Song", May 30- June 1, 1946; 511-4; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Goya The Graphic Work. Stanford Art Gallery. 11 January--3 March 1974, 2003-017; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
    Features "They carried her off" plate 8 from Los Caprichos. Bears red ink stamp "File Copy"
    Art Dept.
  - Graduate Painting, Sculpture and Lithography. Stanford University Gallery May 14-June 16, 1974, 2003-018; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
    Includes photos of Steve Schultz, Margo McDaniels, Marcia Morse, Gary Zerrilla, and Peter Yackulics
  - Graduate Student Organization- Morality of Research, 1969; 5173; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Graduate Students Association- Happy Hour, 1967C7; 5171; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box C7)
  - Graduate Students Association- Happy Hour, 1968; 5172; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Grand Opera House Stanford Night Saturday Evening, Nov. 9th / Walter E. Perkins in The Man from Mexico / the Double Quartette from the Stanford Glee Club in Ccollege Songs / The Stanford Manolin Club, in Specialties [could be 1909, 1915, 1920], 524-42; 14 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Grand Wagnerian Festival, Un-dated; 524-37; 11 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Grape Strike Rally, Un-dated; 905-37; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Greet H. H. Humphey in San Francisco Thursday Sept. 26. Noon Rally at White Plaza. Stanford SDS Committee on Democracy and Electoral Politics., 1968; 905-45; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Guide to the Palaces of Fine Art, Un-dated; 122; 10 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Gunter Grass, 1966; 332; 10 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - H.M.S. Pinafore, The Lass that Loved a Sailor, 1982; 903-16; 14 x 16 inches (Box B3)
  - Handel--Alexander's Feast. The Stanford Symphonic Chorus conducted by James Frieman. Friday, December 4, 1992. Memorial Church., 524-56; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Handel--Judas Maccabaeus presented by the Department of Music at Stanford. University Chorus with Orchestra, Sunday March 1 [no year], 1970s; 2003-011; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
    features painting of Handel by B. Mendelsohn
  - "Hawk Island", Un-dated; 513-51; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - "Hearts and Hands." A Social History in Film of American Women and Quilts., Un-dated (1980s); 905-83; 11 x 17 inches (Box B3)
  - "Hedda Gabler", Un-dated; 513-55; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - "Hell-Bent Fer Heaven", 1923; 513-19; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Hell-Bent Fer Heaven", Un-dated; 513-20; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Hellzapoppin Dance, Un-dated; 5198; 22 x 28 inches (Box D2)
  - Help Save Wayne Morse from the Hawks! We're Going to Oregon. Stanford Committee for New Democratic Politics [1968], 905-56; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Hemingway. A selection of books and manuscripts from the Charles D. Field Collection., 1985; 20117; 18 x 23 inches (Box D2)
  - Henrik Ibsen "Ros Mers Holm", Un-dated; 511-42; 11 x 17 inches (Box C5)
  - Henry Steele Commager, 1969; 380; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Henschels!, Un-dated; 124; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - "High Tor", Un-dated; 511-59; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - History of Film, 1965; 12; 17 x 11 inches (Box A6)
    Films
  - Home Concert of the Stanford Glee and Mandolin Clubs Assembly Hall, Saturday Evening, April 8 [could be 1905- or 1911 or 1916]--handwritten on upper edge: "Now is your chance to ask her to the", 524-50; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
  - Hon. Horace Davis: Talk to Stanford Men., Un-dated; 398; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station Timeline (1 of 2), circa 2000; 2008-01-0; 61 x 18 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Hopkins Marine Station Timeline (2 of 2), circa 2000; 39448; 59 x 18 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - How shall we begin Vietnam Summer. Local--national. Thurs. June 1 [1967] Tresidder 270, 526-04; 12 x 18 inches (Box C4)
  - How will you spend Summer '66? The "y" has countless ideas & info on work projects, travel & study--Thursday March 31--TMU [hand written on poster board], 1966; 905-36; 14.5 x 11.5 inches (Box B2)
  - Humanity Center--Materializing Cultures: Science, Technology, and Medicine in Global Context, 1997; 21702; 17.5x22.5 inches (Box C1)
    Humanity Center
  - I Solisti di Zagreb, 1965; 901-60; 6 x 15 inches (Box A4)
  - Icebound. Owen Davis' tense drama of New England present-day life...director of Gordon Davis. Stanford University Assembly Hall Friday August 1 [probably 1924], 524-15; 22 x 14 inches (Box C5)
  - Illusrated Lecture, 1905-; 312; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - "In a Cold Hotel and the 100st", Un-dated; 511-43; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - In Affiliation with THE AMERICAN BUDDHIST ORDER...the Stanford BUDDHIST Society meets every Thursday at 7:30 P.M...., 1968; 905-59; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
    date is penciled on the poster
  - In Memoriam--Jane Lathrop Stanford, Un-dated; 31; 8x10 inches (Box A1)